F: My name is Farhan Herdian Pradana
F: I'm the representative of my group.
A: My name is Aldian Asmara
A: From State University of Jakarta's Computer Science
F: There's another one, sir. His name is Tantyo but he hasn't joined this call. (sorry, i was at the doctor)
F: Let us start now, sir.
F: So, i've sent you the design yesterday.
Agi: Yes.
F: What do you think of the design?
Agi: The design is...
Agi: From my perspective first, ok?
Agi: So, i made the application...
Agi: I used an old design for it.
Agi: Maybe in the latest version, it would be like that.
Agi: Like the one you, Farhan, made.
Agi: I haven't implemented the searching feature.
Agi: In this current version.
Agi: The view is actually good...
Agi: That you boys have made.
F: Thank you, sir,
F: If there's a chance... Wait, never mind.
F: You have said that this is a temporary design for the application, right sir?
(Losing connection)
F: Ok, so, you said it's a first temporary design. In your application.
Agi: Yes.
F: If there's a time and chance, would you use the design we have made for the application?
Agi: Yes, I might.
Agi: I am considering it.
Agi: But i'm not sure if there's a time for it.
Agi: Have you ever made a similar application?
F: For android, no sir. We have made some for websites.
F: But for this task, we are specifically asked to interview you (an android developer) and ask if-
F: You would take this design or not. Because it will affect our gradings.
F: So, yeah, we're asking about what you think (on our design).
Agi: Generally, nowadays, designs are like that.
Agi: So the design that you made have been adopted by many people...
Agi: In other applications and such.
Agi: In the future, if i have time, maybe i will do the same.
Agi: Like that UX design and umm-
F: UI/UX
Agi: Like you've designed.
Agi: I do think it's good.
F: Aldian, do you a question (for him)?
A: Nope.
F: Oh, ok then. Sir, i think this interview is done.
F: Do you have anything to say (to the people watching this video)?
Agi: Ok so... What semester are you in?
F: We're still in 5th semester.
Agi: I thought you guys are making an application. So i wanted to know... So, never mind on that.
Agi: I'll take this as criticism that's telling me:
Agi: Your designs are... the way that they are.
Agi: There are data list there, like for example...
Agi: That religious study (list).
Agi: It's (my design) supposed to be like that (in your design).
Agi: There should be a search feature.
Agi: I thought you would make it for me.
F: No sir. We've only been told to design it for you.
Agi: Yeah, yeah. There aren't enough features in the current app.
F: Ok, sir. I think we're done now.
F: Thank you so much for your time, sir.
F: You have helped us with our assignments and we are really grateful for it.
Agi: You're welcome. I hope you're doing well in you assignment.
F: Yes, sir. Thank you.
F: I will now close the interview call, sir.
F: Oh, also, forgive us if we've misworded something.
Agi: Yeah, it's fine.
Agi: I will leave now, ok?
Everyone else: Yes, sir.
A: Thank you, sir.